<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NewFeatures</string>
    <string name="long_string">Test your apps for compatibility with Android 9. Just download a device system image, install your current app, and test in areas where behavior changes may affect the app. Update your code and publish, using the app\'s current platform targeting. \nStart by targeting Android 9 and supporting its behavior changes. When you\'re ready, extend your apps with new features and APIs.</string>
    <string name="linkify">Yes! Can you go to Mestizo? It\'s 103 Hampstead Rd.</string>
    <string name="long_text">It\'s hard not to stop and stare when you see a member of Toronto\'s Mounted Police Unit patrolling the streets: seeing horses in general is a rare occurrence for the average urban Torontonian — seeing them trotting down King Street is an even bigger trip.

But, given we\'re in the age of speedy Ford Interceptor cop cruisers with engines of 188 horsepower, why do we still have police officers on actual horses (which, while majestic, are a pretty antiquated way of getting from point A to B) riding through the city?

Contrary to what many people think, the Mounted Unit has no affiliation with the RCMP, though it\'s easy to see why you\'d make that mistake.

Toronto\'s Mounted Unit is part of the municipal Toronto Police Service, and unlike the RCMP\'s occasional use of horses — which is purely ceremonial — Toronto officers on horseback can do anything that cops in cars can do.

Aside from attending events like the Queen\'s Plate opening and funerals for major politicians, mounted officers (like bike cops) can enforce street level laws.

That includes things like pulling over vehicles, patrolling the Entertainment District for drunken shenanigans on weekend nights, and standing guard at planned protests and rallies alongside other officers in the TPS.

"The Mounted Unit is a support unit, we support the other divisions\' needs," says Sergeant Kris McCarthy, who has been with the Mounted Unit for 20 years.

Since the they\'re based out of the Horse Palace at the CNE, you\'re more likely to see the Mounted Unit patrolling nearby downtown Divisions 11, 14, 51, and 52, walking in the bike lanes.

Speaking of which, let\'s address the poop.

"It\'s been something that\'s been spoken of for many, many years," says Sgt. McCarthy about the horse manure that\'s sometimes left in downtown bike lanes, to the ire of bikers.

"Horse manure is completely non-harmful to humans…unlike dogs, they\'re hay eaters, it\'s no different than leaving grass clipping on your front lawn."

While there are diapers and manure-catching apparatuses for horses, he says those can be hazards for officers. He recommends calling 311, waiting for the City to clean the streets, or just waiting for the manure to dry out and blow away in the wind. </string>
</resources>
